<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ThubLogin</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="main_text"> The demand-supply gap scenario, exponential opportunities
        and dynamic challenges in the 21st century call for a change in our thinking on
        engineering practice and education. A transformation on the current engineering
        education is the need of the hour. Growth of new knowledge together with rapidly
        evolving technological skills, the skill to communicate across disciplines, the
        ability to lead team-centered projects, contextualized problem formulation, and
        hands-on experience are the present demands of the global industry. On contrary
        to the present demands, students churned out from engineering colleges are not
        equipped to meet the current industry needs due to the growing gap between
        engineering practice, education and research which requires a lot of concern.
        As a timely response, it is this concern for the student that has led Aditya to
        initiate T-Hub: a perfect launch pad to the job world. T-Hub trains students in
        various disciplines beyond technological labels besides equipping them with skills
        and creativity required for advancement in their careers. Through its various programs
        t-hub provides adequate opportunities for an unmatched knowledge base by imparting all
        necessary skills to students and makes them job ready.  </string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
</resources>
